Leonard? Leonard?
(Leonard(following Sheldon into living room):)- What?
- I was analyzing our lie...
(Sheldon:)...and I believe we're in danger
of Penny seeing through the ruse.
- How?
- Simple.
If she were to log on to www.
socalphysicsgroup.org/activities/other...
...click on upcoming events, scroll to
seminars, download the PDF schedule...
(Sheldon:)...and look for the seminar
on molecular positronium, then...
...bippity boppity boo,
our pants are metaphorically on fire.
(Sheldon:)Well, sir, my trousers
will not be igniting today.
Penny?
(Sheldon:)Good morning.
- Do you have any idea what time it is?
- Of course I do.
(Sheldon:)My watch is linked to the atomic clock
in Boulder, Colorado.
It's accurate to one-tenth of a second.
(Sheldon:)As I'm saying this
it occurs to me once again...
(Sheldon:)...your question may
have been rhetorical.
(Penny:)What do you want?